[Music]
[音乐]
本教程是关于锯齿形褶皱
this tutorial is about zigzag folds
这是不言而喻的
四个平面，两个标签将其粘合到
this tutorial is about zigzag folds
here's is self-explanatory it's just
页面，您可以在这里有所不同
另一个例子是基于
here's is self-explanatory it's just
four planes two tabs gluing it to the
平行四边形，所以重要的是
弹出窗口上的该长度与
four planes two tabs gluing it to the
page you can vary it somewhat here's
这个长度基于
弹出窗口与此上的长度相同
page you can vary it somewhat here's
another example this is based on the
粘在底座上的底座
他们有角度，所以他们在同一时间见面
another example this is based on the
parallelogram so the important thing is
指向脊椎也可以玩
围绕这两种类型
parallelogram so the important thing is
this length on the pop-up is the same as
折痕都是垂直的，但是你可以
实际上改变折痕并使它们
this length on the pop-up is the same as
this length on the base this length on
向内或向外倾斜，这会给您更多
有趣的雕塑优势
this length on the base this length on
the pop-up is the same as this length on
所以这是一个例子
中央折痕，你有两个
the pop-up is the same as this length on
the base where it's glued to the base
外部的指向
中间，然后在此示例中
the base where it's glued to the base
they're angled so they meet at the same
中央折痕，你有那些
指出两个折痕，但仍然
they're angled so they meet at the same
point on the spine you can also play
只是卡住的两个地方
然后当你建立这些
point on the spine you can also play
around with it these two types the
创建可以内置的沟渠
是的，如果我们仔细看一下
around with it these two types the
creases are all vertical but you can
你有你有这三个沟渠
你可以建立第一个
creases are all vertical but you can
actually vary the creases and make them
我从这个开始，所以这里这些
你会想到的两个沟渠
actually vary the creases and make them
lean in or out and that gives you more
通常建在这里
所以这是一个例子
lean in or out and that gives you more
interesting sculptural strengths to play
这些房子的基本曲折
内置在枪里
interesting sculptural strengths to play
with so here's one example there's the
如果我把它折叠起来，你会看到它的状态
被粘在下面
with so here's one example there's the
central crease and you've got the two
房子是基于平行四边形
是的，我只有一个广告
central crease and you've got the two
outer ones pointing in towards the
例如，这是童话般的村庄
bilats低腰，这是你
outer ones pointing in towards the
middle and then in this example this is
有一个锯齿形的折叠和房子
基于内置的平行四边形
middle and then in this example this is
the central crease and you've got those
那些沟渠，你还有另一个
之字形折叠在那里，然后这些之字形
the central crease and you've got those
two creases pointing out but it's still
形状在我的作品中得到了更全面的解释
书弹出设计器纸力学
two creases pointing out but it's still
just the two places that it's stuck down
[音乐]